[beeping]
[humming happily]
[Anzu] It's finally here.
Ishiai Koji's cat book!
I love that Mom sends
pictures of Momohiki,
but this is an extra cat boost for my day.
Let the healing begin!
[smooches]
[Anzu] Huh? Has it already been a month
since Kazuki moved in?
Guess he'll be finding a new place soon.
Living with Junta and Kazuki
has been surprisingly fun.
It'll be strange when he moves out.
ARISA: CAN WE MEET?
[Anzu] Speaking of strange, I wonder
who that text was from--
-[man] I know, right?
-[grunts]
-[can clanks]
-[man grunts]
[Anzu] My book!
[sighs in relief]
What the hell do you think you're doing?
I was just waiting
for the light to change.
[Anzu] He bumped into me.
I should be the one yelling.
It's all thanks to you
that I dropped my coffee.
-And ruined my shoes.
-[gasps]
-[man] You're gonna pay for that!
-[Anzu] Hey!
-Uh…
-That's enough.
[Anzu] Huh?
You're the one who bumped into her.
[gasping]
Ah, dude. You're, like, crazy hot.
What do you say, you pay back
your little friend's debt with a date?
[man laughing mischievously]
[grunts in pain]
-Don't ever touch me.
-[man] Ow…
Now apologize to her.
It's just a stupid book!
[grunts]
Just a book?
[Anzu] You have no idea what I've lost!
[shouting] This book is worth
hours of healing!
I curse you!
May stray cats infest your house
and soak your bed in cat pee!
You're gonna drill straight into my brain!
-[growling]
-[screams]
I'm sorry!
-[man] Ow!
-Uh…
[man] My head… the pain.
That chick's crazy.
-[snorts]
-[startled gasps]
Maybe next time
you'll be a little bit more respectful.
[all gasp]
-Let's go.
-[Anzu blows raspberry]
-Your book okay? Sorry about those jerks.
-[gasps]
Heh?
[sighs in relief]
[Anzu exclaims]
Oh yeah, the book's fine.
Thanks for saving me.
Oh my gosh, she'll think I'm in love!
I hope I don't look as dumb
as I feel right now!
Did you really
curse him with a cat-pee-soaked mattress?
[Anzu] It was all I could think of.
You can never get that smell out.
-[Tsukasa] Arisa.
-[both] Huh?
Hey, Tsukasa.
Kazuki?
Hoshino? You know each other?
Hoshino, like…
Wait, are you Anzu Hoshino?
Me? Um…
I'm Arisa, Tsukasa's big sister.
Thanks for looking after him.
[chuckles]
Uh, legendary good looks
run in your family.
So bright, can't look directly at it!
[Tsukasa] You're an idiot.
[theme music]
[birds chirping]
#8 THE PHOENIX RISES! I AM A BIRD!
Thanks for having me. Are you sure
that I'm not barging in here?
Of course not.
Thanks again
for letting Tsukasa stay here.
A month is a long time.
No, not at all.
Really, it's been awesome
having him around.
[Anzu] Not to mention
this whole thing is my fault.
My mother and I
should have introduced ourselves sooner.
-To be honest, we were a bit surprised.
-[grumbles]
We didn't think he'd be staying this long.
Between the pipe bursting
and the new phone, it's been chaotic.
So I figured it was probably
best for me to come out
and get the details in person.
Oh yeah, that makes sense.
[Anzu] The phone…
Yeah, that was my fault too.
Oh. Hey, would you like
something to drink?
I think we have some iced tea, or, um…
-[Tsukasa] Uh, there's a fresh pitcher.
-Oh, that would be great.
[chuckles]
[Arisa clears throat]
Better let Mom know everything's okay.
[Tsukasa] So, did something happen
at the station? You looked frazzled.
Oh. This guy bumped into me,
then tried to pick a fight with me.
[Tsukasa] What?
But your sister totally saved me.
Those guys didn't stand a chance.
You know what? Your sister's really cool.
Yeah, but she had a tendency
to find trouble.
I'm sorry that happened.
Nah, it's fine,
'cause I cursed him with a mattress
completely soaked in cat pee!
-So yeah, it's all good.
-[muffled laugh]
[Tsukasa] Seriously?
A mattress soaked in cat pee?
No, it really is the worst!
[chuckles]
[Anzu] Sorry to keep you waiting.
All good, thanks.
Kazuki, I'm just curious.
Why did you wanna go to our school
and live alone?
[both gasp]
[both sigh]
[Anzu] Uh, you don't have to answer that.
I shouldn't have asked.
-[whimpers]
-Hmm… Well, how do I say this?
-Huh?
-[soft chuckle]
Our father's a real piece of garbage.
SHIT
Piece of garbage?
Yup. That's why our mom decided
it was best for Tsukasa
to go to school out here.
Oh.
I'm not wrong, am I?
No.
I was really worried
when I heard you'd be living alone.
I'm relieved you're staying
with someone sweet like Anzu.
[phone vibrates]
Oh, Makoto.
Um, hey.
What's up?
-[Arisa] Who's Makoto?
-[Anzu] He's a friend from school.
Oh.
Hey, what's Tsukasa like
at school, anyway?
Well, uh, he's popular
but keeps to himself.
Being reserved makes everyone
like him even more.
And you?
-You seem to like him too, huh?
-[chokes]
[spits, gags]
Huh?
[in deep voice]
It's not like that.
I swear on my unborn descendants.
[Arisa] That's a bit extreme.
In fact, I didn't like him
when I first met him.
But…
I'm glad I took the time
to get to know him better.
'Cause, you know,
now he's a really great friend.
[Arisa chuckles softly]
You know, he used to be
a really social kid.
He was always smiling,
befriending everyone he met.
I can't picture that.
[Arisa chuckles]
I know, right?
There was a problem
back when he was in junior high.
Ever since then, he sort of shut down.
So before, the way he was laughing
with you, I haven't seen that side
of my little brother
in a really long time.
Huh?
You bring it out of him, Anzu.
Really, it's not--
-[door shuts]
-[both] Huh?
He wanted me to go to a movie,
but I think he really just wanted
someone to vent to.
-[Anzu] About what?
-Oh…
Something about his sister
stealing his last pudding.
MAKOTO
IT WAS DELICIOUS
[chuckles]
Tell him next time
to write his name on it.
[Tsukasa] He did. She ate it anyway.
Hmm. There's no stronger grudge
than one held over food.
Is it that big a deal?
I don't make the rules.
[light music]
About your friend, Anzu.
She's sweet. I'm just surprised
you're friends with her.
[chuckles]
I thought
you were still avoiding all girls.
[sighs]
Yeah, I know. I wasn't planning on it.
But she's different.
I feel more at ease with her.
Tsukasa, why don't you just
stay here a while?
Huh?
Calm down, it's a joke.
-[sighs in relief]
-Uh… uh…
Uh, well…
[Anzu] I don't mind if you don't mind.
Hm?
You've been so helpful around here.
And maybe it's just me,
but I think it's been a lot of fun
living with you and Junta.
[Anzu] Not to mention Riri's scheming
if you leave Junta and I alone.
Most importantly,
you're the only one brave enough
to kill all those bugs!
-[groans]
-[Tsukasa chuckles]
If it's that important to you,
then I guess I'll stay.
Hm.
[sighs in relief]
Yeah? This will be great!
There's another show
I've been dying to watch.
Sure.
I get it now. That's why
you never wanted to talk about her.
You were embarrassed I'd figure it out.
That she makes you smile again.
Um…
-Wait, do you like--
-It's not like that.
With Hoshino, I can be myself.
For me, that's all I need.
[Tsukasa sighs]
[Arisa] Okay.
[soft music]
[water running]
[Anzu] I'm glad
I met Kazuki's sister today.
I learned a lot more about him.
[door opens]
Hey, you're back.
You have the coolest sister.
I loved getting to meet her.
[gasps]
I should have worn something nicer.
This outfit sucks.
I really assumed you thought
that outfit was appropriate
to meet guests.
No way.
I learned a lot
when we went shopping together.
I've tried to be more mindful
about what I wear since then.
[Anzu] Man, I wish I had
a big sister like her.
Hoshino.
What Arisa said
about why I lived by myself…
Yeah?
Uh, uh--
[exhales deeply]
Never mind. Maybe another day.
Hmm…
[Anzu] Uh, okay.
[Anzu] Is it just me or…
-[Riri] Is this warm feeling friendship?
-[grunts]
Or is this excitement? Love!
Yay! Great job, Anzu, I'm so proud of you!
You were able to get
his big sister's approval,
even just like that.
I tell you how can you find love,
it's so fulfilling.
-Now, let's keep this up--
-You know what? I didn't miss you one bit!
[Anzu roars]
-[slaps]
-Come on!
A FEW DAYS LATER
In order to address low birth rate issues,
Anzu was gifted a real-life dating sim
called Romantic Thriller.
And after many perfect scenarios,
I am reporting that there has been
zero romantic development.
I can't turn this in!
[frustrated groan]
Clearly, I have a lot more research to do.
I have an excellent idea!
-We can go on a date.
-What?
[Riri] I need to experience
what a real-life date is like,
so you and I will go on a mock date.
A mock date?
What are you even talking about?
I'm so over your nonsense.
[chuckling]
Aw, don't be such a meanie!
-Ha!
-[explosion]
-[Anzu] Huh?
-What if I look like this instead?
[chuckles]
[Anzu] Wait!
There's a boy version of you too?
[groans]
Whatever. Doesn't change anything.
I'm not asking you to do this for free.
-[Anzu] Huh?
-[Rio] I'll buy you those cat pajamas
you saw in the mall.
The one with the hoodies and tail.
[in deep voice]
It's a deal.
[groans in pain]
Let go!
Whoo! Can't believe I'm on my first date!
Tell me…
[bright music]
Why did I have to dress up for this?
It's a date.
We're not hanging out
at a rest stop for truckers.
Hey! Do I really dress that badly?
Yep, just the worst.
Now, on with our date!
Ugh!
-[whimpers]
-Easy there, I'm not some sort of pervert.
Holding hands is what you do on dates.
I don't care. I don't want people
getting the wrong idea about us.
-[grunts]
-Hmm…
[Rio] I'll buy you another cat shirt!
[Anzu grunts]
-Fine, then hold my hand.
-Ow, ow, ouch!
So, where are we going?
The most classic of dating activities.
The movies.
[laughter]
[Rio] A romantic movie always
gets the couple in the mood for love.
Slowly their hands touch.
-[girl gasps]
-Huh?
[Rio] And then, their lips touch.
[smooching]
You're twisted.
[indistinct chatter]
Is there anything good out right now?
Oh, any cat movies?
[Rio] No cats! We're on a date,
so we're definitely watching
a romantic movie!
ETERNAL STAR
What? That looks so lame.
One of those tearjerkers
where the girl dies in the end.
Tearjerkers are great!
So much romance,
it'll be the perfect reference material!
Using this kind of movie
is a reference…
doesn't bode well for me.
[Makoto groans]
That was so good!
We've got to do this more often.
-[Tsukasa] Yeah.
-[Makoto] Hey, look!
-Need the bathroom first.
-[Makoto] Hosshi!
-[both] Huh?
-[Makoto] Hey, you!
-[Anzu gasps]
-Looking good all dressed up.
Kazuki, Makoto.
-Huh?
-Uh?
[gasps]
-[Anzu] Oh crap!
-[Anzu grunting]
How's it going?
I'm Anzu's cousin, Rio. Rio Fushigi.
I'm Riri's twin brother.
[Anzu] Yeah, nice backstory.
This is just great.
All the people in this town
and we had to run into these two?
Wait, didn't he set this up?
All right, we better get going then.
We're on a date.
-[smacks]
-Hey, don't say stuff like that.
Ignore him.
Rio just likes to mess around sometimes.
Bye!
-See ya, Hosshi. Oh, and Hosshi's cousin.
-[growls]
They seem oddly close
for being cousins, don't you think?
[Anzu grunts]
What's your problem?
Calm down, it's a mock date.
Gotta treat it like the real thing.
You're gonna give them
the wrong idea about me.
I'll sue you for defamation!
The lady doth protest too much.
[Anzu] Strange. Usually, he'd get Kazuki
and the others involved
in some crazy dating scenarios.
Maybe he really is trying
to learn about dating.
Too bad for him,
whatever he learns here,
I'll just destroy it!
-[chuckles mischievously]
-What's with that face?
Smiling weird like that makes you look
like you're coming unhinged.
There's nothing better than popcorn